<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SCC App</string>
    <string name="test_placeholder">TERMS AND CONDITIONS\n

    </string>
    <string name="body">• The SCC App (Skin Condition Classifier App) is an application that allows users to upload images for skin condition classification using AI model.
        The SCC App only serves as a Prototype application meant for the group\'s fulfillment of undergraduate thesis and is expected to
        not have any updates in the future.\n\n
    • The application only requires one image to be uploaded to the cloud for the AI model to classify the skin condition. It will be temporarily stored in our AWS platform.
        For more information regarding their services, please refer to the AWS Privacy Policy.\n\n

        • Any images that are used for model inference are not stored in any database nor will be used for any succeeding trainings.\n\n
        • Even if the application has been verified with doctors and dermatologists, this application is not meant to be used to substitute and/or replace actual doctors;
        It is still highly advised to see an actual doctor regardless of the result from this application to ensure proper identification of your skin condition.\n\n
        • By clicking the button below, the user has read the terms and condition and acknowledges the statements above.
    </string>
    <string name="testinfo">"• You have healthy skin. It appears smooth, hydrated, and undamaged. The skin is the outer protective" +
                        "layer of the body, and it is good to keep healthy.\n" +
                        "To keep your skin healthy, you can do the following:\n" +
                        "• Apply moisturizer at least once a day\n" +
                        "• Avoid damage from UV, apply sunscreen if necessary and wear protective clothing\n" +
                        "• Avoid taking hot showers to prevent skin from drying\n" +
                        "• Stay hydrated to maintain moisture in the skin"));
</string>
</resources>